你让我们把衣服处理掉
You told us to get rid of the clothes.
我们照做了  它们再也不会回来了
Oh we got rid of 'em, all right. They're never coming back.
你们两个简直绝了  到底为什么要叫我过来
You two are impossible. Why did you even call me here?
因为你是卡洛琳公主  你什么都能处理
Because you're Princess Carolyn, you can fix anything.
这倒是  但是你们不能在自家草坪上点火啊
That's true. But you can't start a fire on your lawn.
现在正是旱季...  旱季
There's a drought and-- There's a drought.
你作为一位细心的丈夫  处理掉了草坪
You, thoughtful husband that you are, got rid of your lawn,
换成了抗旱的绿化植被
and replaced it with drought-resistant landscaping.
这个办法能行  我得打几个电话
This could work. I got to make a few phone calls.
谢谢  你最棒了
Thanks. You're the best.
我跟你说  我得想想办法
I tell you, I've got half a mind to go over
好好教训一下臭鼬那个罪魁祸首
and give it to that skunk for starting this whole darn thing.